tessco.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Statement - TESSCO.com

_Last Updated: October, 2008_

#### Your Privacy is Important To Us

For this reason, we have established a privacy policy that safeguards your personal information, and we are committed to protecting its confidentiality:

  * We will limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business, provide you with the highest quality service, and offer you opportunities we think will be of interest.
  * We will not disclose any individual information except in the limited circumstances described below.
  * We wholeheartedly support strong and effective privacy guidelines and practices on the Web and believe that these will enhance everyone's use of the Web.

#### Collected Information

We collect information about you when you register with us or purchase products from us, from our use of "cookies" and other tracking technology as you access our web site, and when you email us. (A "cookie" is information we place on your computer to help us identify you or your preferences or interests as reflected by your visits to our website.)

#### What do we do with this information?

We use personal information you provide to us — such as your name and address, telephone or fax number, or email address — to fulfill your orders, to contact you with questions or information about your orders, and to provide you with information that you request. We may also use this information and information about your interests and preferences in our continuing efforts to keep our customers and friends informed about new and exciting products, services, and promotions that we offer, which may include mailings, telephone calls, and email mailings.

##### A Few More Words About "Cookies"

We use "cookies" to enable you to properly access, display, or read information on our web site, to permit information to follow you from page to page, and to keep track of your interests and preferences. You can set your browser to alert you whenever you are about to receive a "cookie" and then you can choose not to accept it. If you do so, however, you may not be able to use TESSCO.com.

#### Email Address Use

Email addresses are used internally for order completion/confirmation, product/service communications, and for internal aggregate data analysis.

##### Email Opt Out

At TESSCO, we completely respect your online time and privacy. In addition to online order confirmation we also hope to keep you informed of special offers, product news, upcoming industry events or other news which we hope you'll find highly relevant.

We value our relationship with you and hope that find our electronic communications to be helpful and informative. You may, however choose to opt out of receiving future promotional communication from TESSCO. In compliance with the 2003 Can SPAM Act, we offer the ability to opt out of receiving communications from us at any time by sending us a message indicating your request to: [optout@tessco.com](mailto:optout@tessco.com), responding via a direct opt-out link on our email communications, or by writing to us at: TESSCO Technologies Incorporated, 11126 McCormick Road, Hunt Valley, MD 21031-1494; c/o MARCOM.

#### Independent Contractors

We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services to us such as sending email, analyzing customer lists and data, or provide consulting services. These third parties will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose.

Except for this sharing, we will not intentionally disclose any personal information about you unless we are required to do so by law. We use reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure and to disclose it only to third parties we believe will use it appropriately. We are not responsible, however, for breaches of security or for any actions of third parties who receive the information. We also link to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other web sites, and we urge you to examine their policies before disclosing any information.

#### Policy Updates

Please check our web site periodically for updates as TESSCO may update this policy from time to time. Policy updates shall be effective the date the change is posted on the site. Notice of any material changes in the manner in which TESSCO handles personally identifiable information under this policy will be provided on the Site.

#### How to Contact Us

If you wish to contact us - to correct personal information or elect not to receive communications either from us or from third parties or just to ask us any questions about these matters - email us at [ecom@TESSCO.com](mailto:ecom@TESSCO.com). 

Back to Top
